YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
时间轴：godwuwen
后期： 鱼骨头  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： vero  非燕  阿蘅  猫中之王
后期： 鱼骨头  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期：鱼骨头 字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十二集
孩子们  我有没有告诉过你们
Kids, have I ever told you
我和你们父亲的浪漫史
the story of how I met your father?
好吧  我就跳过这段
Well, I'll just skip ahead
直接说我告诉他我怀孕的事吧
to the moment I told him I was pregnant.
怎么回事
W... What happened?
我晕过去了吗
Did I pass out?
不完全是
Not exactly.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
你确定你不是单纯的变胖吗
Are you sure you're not just getting fat?
当然
Oh, yeah.
好吧  你怀孕了
So, um, you're pregnant.
是啊
Yeah.
怎么你的胸还是依旧平坦
Looks like nobody told your boobs.
怎么回事
What happened?
-我晕过去了吗  -我打死你
- Did I pass out? - Oh, my god...
女侠  手下留情
Please stop hitting me!
你...
Hey. Are...
你确定你真的...
Are you sure you're...
不  我还没验呢
Well, no, not positive.
我例假迟了一周
I'm a week late.
可我从来都很准
But I'm never late;
这点一直让我引以为豪
it's a point of pride with me.
为了保险起见  我周一要去看医生
I'm going to go see the doctor on Monday to find out for sure.
在那之前  不要告诉任何人
Until then, not a word of this to anyone.
凯文也不行吗
Not even Kevin?
有可能是他的呀
I mean, it's probably his.
我可是花了多年时间  调教我的子弟兵们往反方向游
I've spent years training my boys to swim the other way.
我还没跟凯文睡过呢
Kevin and I haven't had sex yet.
如果我怀孕了  你就是孩子他爸
If I'm pregnant, you're the dad.
真是太好了
That's wonderful!
我要当爸爸了
I'm gonna be a daddy!
好了  爸比喝威士忌
Okay, one scotch for me,
妈咪喝烈酒杯盛的冰茶
one iced tea on the rocks glass for Mommy.
-住嘴  -抱歉抱歉
- Stop it. - Sorry, sorry.
这事要保密
Keeping it secret.
糟糕  我把我那杯给你了
Oop, I think I gave you the wrong one.
来  让我...
Here, let me just...
给我  松开  放手
Give it to me. Drop... let go.
让我把酒拿回来
Take it away from you.
巴尼  你为什么这么高兴
Barney, why are you so happy about this?
因为这是件大喜事
Because this is perfect.
我一直想当个爸爸
I want to be a dad.
这可不是什么好消息
This is not good news.
我还有个男友
I have a boyfriend.
是啊  但如果没有凯文呢
Yeah, but if Kevin weren't around...
这都无关紧要了
It doesn't matter!
我不想要孩子
I don't want kids.
我从没想过要孩子
I've never wanted kids,
从不  再过一百万年
and never, in a million years,
我也绝不会想要孩子
will I ever want kids.
抱歉  孩子们
Sorry, kids.
我不能有孩子
I can't have a baby.
大家好
Hey, guys!
猜猜这是什么
Guess what this is!
你的一只袜子  答对了  你个大巨人
One of your socks? Boom! You're huge.
不  这是我们未出生儿子的圣诞袜
No, it's our unborn son's Christmas stocking.
从我和莉莉结婚那天起
Grandma Gunderson started knitting it
冈德森祖母就开始织了
the day Lily and I got married.
直到临终前也没能织完
She died before she could finish.
我真想念圣诞袜
I miss stockings.
我继父科林特逼我们舍弃一切
My stepdad Clint made us get rid of anything
会使他想起圣诞节商业化的东西
that reminds him of the commercialization of Christmas.
你说过他有打扮成圣诞老人的模样呀
I thought you said he dresses up as Santa.
是啊  但是为了抗议性别成见
Yeah, but, uh, to protest gender stereotypes,
他打扮成女圣诞老人
he plays Santa as a woman.
不过他还留着胡子
Though, he keeps the beard.
结果就是弄巧成拙
The result is disturbing.
我们该走了
Well, we should go.
得去"婴儿总动员"商店
We have to get to We B Babies
订购新生儿欢迎会上的礼品
so that we can register for our shower.
我去不了
No can do.
我在搞一个大工程
Um, I have a big project that I'm working on.
这是理查德・霍德曼在东梅多的房子
This is Richard Holdman's house in East Meadow.
去年  他家成了横跨三州最受欢迎的
Last year, he had the most visited Christmas display
圣诞装饰景观
in the tri-state area.
但今年不会了  知道为什么吗
But not this year. You know why?
因为大软糖空降此地
Because Big Fudge has come to town,
大软糖是马修学校酒吧打游戏机时用的代号
他还带来了两个朋友
and he brought his two friends:
曼海姆  和压路机
Mannheim... Steamroller.
曼海姆压路机  美国著名圣诞歌曲乐队组合
比赛开始
Game on.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
只是...
Uh, it's just, um...
我讨厌曼海姆压路机乐队
I hate Mannheim Steamroller.
你就不能用别人吗
Isn't there anyone else you can use?
拜托  如果不用压路机  我还能用谁啊
Come on! Who am I gonna use if not the Steamroller?!
我不知道  AC/DC如何
I don't know. AC/DC?
AC/DC  澳洲重金属乐队
AC/DC
AC/DC?
罗宾  你知不知道
Robin, do you have any idea
曼海姆压路机  何以得名
why they call them Mannheim Steamroller?
因为他们的摇滚
Because they rock...
又劲爆  又有节日气氛
so hard, so festively,
就像压路机那样威力无穷
that steam comes out of your brain.
让人服服帖帖
As it melts.
那我得自己去"婴儿总动员"了
So I have to go to We B Babies by myself?
罗宾和我跟你一起去
Robin and I will go with you.
婴儿总动员
巴尼  我们干嘛跟来
Barney, what are we doing here?
我想让你知道生小孩
I want to show you that having a kid
没什么好怕的
is nothing to be afraid of.
孩子们  别闹腾了
Kids. Stop.
开始采购  表单第一项
Okay, first on the registry:
乳头黄油滋养霜
nipple butter.
你要是母乳喂养
As you breast-feed,
你的乳头就会变长  大约长四英寸
your nipples stretch out, like, four inches
还会引起干燥和皲裂
and get all dry and cracked.
乳头滋养霜能防止乳头干裂出血
The nipple butter stops the bleeding.
我四英寸长的乳头不但干裂  还会出血
My four-inch nipples are going to crack and bleed?!
是啊  可宝宝咬着你干裂出血的乳头时
Yes, but while the baby is gnawing on your bleeding nips,
看她穿的衣服多可爱呀
look what she'll be wearing.
疯子杜安
Insane Duane?
巴尼
Barney?
那还是在认识我和泰德叔叔前
Insane Duane was your father's best friend,
疯子杜安是你们爸爸的死党
back in the days before he met me or your Uncle Ted.
我们准备去她家了
We're going back to her place.
一击即中
Boom!
好样的  你赢了
All right, you win!
这是奖励你说了一个词就钓上了一个妞
Here's 20 for picking up a girl with only one word.
再奖励你二十  因为你用的那个词是"擎天柱"
And here's another 20 for that word being "Boner."
谢谢
Thank you.
一小时后这里见  等我玩完了...
I'll meet you back here in an hour when I'm done with, uh...
管她叫什么呢
Ah, who cares what her name is;
反正不过是过眼云烟
she won't be around long enough for it to matter.
漂亮
Nice!
亲爱的  这是我朋...
Honey, this is my frien...
真不敢相信  那之后我就没见过你了
I can't believe I haven't seen you around.
自从希拉和我打了个快炮后
Well, after Sheila and I had that quickie,
我的生活就是三点一线  陪玩  幼儿园  便便
my life's been playdates, preschools and poops.
我好多年没去过酒吧了
I haven't set foot in a bar in years.
难道你戒酒了
You stopped drinking?
不  唯有酒能解千愁
Oh, I still drink.
阴道镇痛麻醉喷雾
Vaginal numbing spray.
显然  生完孩子后
Apparently, after child birth,
你的阴道就跟拳王洛奇的脸一样伤痕累累
your hoo-ha looks like Rocky Balboa's face.
-你不能生小孩  -我不能生小孩
- You can't have a baby! - I can't have a baby!
第二天  我们去看了医生
The next day, we went to the doctor.
是这样  特布罗斯基太太
Well, Mrs. Scherbatsky,
我肯定  你和你丈夫
I'm sure that you and your husband...
他不是我丈夫
Uh, he's not my husband.
真对不起
Oh, I'm so sorry.
那就是你的男友
Your boyfriend then.
他不是我男友
He's not my boyfriend.
我晕啊
Oh, bozhe.
那好  我就开门见山说吧
All right, well, I will just cut to the chase.
等等  等等
Wait! Wait.
好吧
All right.
好了
Okay.
好  准备好了  很好
All right, we're ready. Good.
你  没怀孕
You are not pregnant.
太好了
Yeah!
-太棒了  -就是
- Oh, yeah! - Yeah!
我就说哪有这么容易中奖呀
That's what I'm talking about!
对  你知道  你知道
Yeah, you know, you know!
再次抱歉  孩子们
Again, sorry kids.
先生
Hey, mister.
你准备把这些圣诞灯全挂上吗
Are you putting up all these Christmas lights?
小子  等我一旦完工
Oh, kid, by the time I'm done,
就算你在外太空  也能看到我的惊世之作
you're gonna be able to see this son of a bitch from outer space.
真酷
Ah, cool.
我想在我们家房子上装彩灯
I wanted to put lights on our house,
可我爸爸不是忙着工作  就是忙别的事情
but my dad says he's too busy with work and stuff.
要不这样吧  你下周末来我家
Hey, what do you say, uh, you come back here next weekend
给我打打下手
and help me out?
好
Yeah!
就这么说定了
You've got yourself a deal.
我叫斯科特
I'm Scott.
我是埃里克森先生
I'm... Mr. Eriksen.
谢谢  埃先生
Thanks, Mr. E.
埃先生
Mr. E.
看来某个小鬼刚赢得
Looks like some little scamp just earned the right
给小耶稣戴上维京队头盔的殊荣
to put the Vikings helmet on baby Jesus.
圣诞彩灯上会给小耶稣带上皇冠
而维京队是马修家乡明尼苏达州的橄榄球队
后来几天  在我尽情享受
Later that week, as I was enjoying every second
没有怀孕的每一刻时
of not being pregnant...
下集《少女妈咪》预告...
Next on Teenage Mommies...
可你说你会看好贝拉
But you said you would watch Bella.
我还要去拉拉队训练呢
I have cheerleading practice.
还好我不象你  布雷斯
Sucks to be you, Braces.
你好哟
Yello!
好  我可以去复诊
Uh, yeah, I can come back in.
罗宾  我们上周做了几项检测
Robin, we ran some tests last week.
我知道这会让你很难接受
This is going to be difficult to hear.
然后医生说了一堆医学术语...
And then the doctor said a bunch of medical stuff that...
反正重点是这句话
well, the gist of it was this.
我不能生孩子
I can't have a baby.
对  你不能生孩子
No. You can't have a baby.
太好了
Uh, great.
我是说  其实也没那么好
Uh, well, I mean, um, not-not great.
反正我从来都不想生孩子
I mean, I've never wanted kids,
如果这事发生在别人身上的话就...
so if it has to happen to someone...
罗宾  你有可以倾诉的对象吗
Robin, is there anyone you can talk to about this?
或许跟好友说一下
Perhaps a close friend?
我知道我能找朋友倾诉
I knew I could have talked to my friends.
可我已经料想到
But, it's just, I already knew
他们的种种反应了
exactly how they would all react.
为了哄我开心  泰德会大费周章
Ted would go into overdrive trying to make me feel better.
你要吃点舒心美食
You need comfort food.
炸鸡  汉堡配芝士  土豆泥
Fried chicken, mac and cheese, mashed potatoes.
打开礼物  我来给你揉肩
Open your present, I'll work on these shoulders.
好了  深呼吸  放轻松  吃鸡
Okay, just breathe, relax, eat your chicken.
快  吃  吸气
Come on, eat, breathe,
开礼物  呼气  开啊  快吃
open it, breathe, open it, eat.
罗宾  你怎么那么紧绷呀
Robin, why are you so tense?!
莉莉会悲痛欲绝
Lily would just implode.
而我居然还不停地唠叨孩子的事
And here I've been going on and on about babies.
我真不够朋友
Oh, I am such a bad friend!
最后搞得我要反过来安慰她
And I'd wind up comforting her.
没事的
It's okay.
你就冲我脸狠劲来一拳吧
You have to punch me in the face!
马修会问我一大堆
Marshall would ask me a ton of questions
我自己都无法回答的问题
I don't know the answers to.
-你考虑过收养吗  -这个...
- Have you thought about adoption? - Um, well...
你这是家族遗传的不孕不育吗
Does this kind of thing run in your family?
你上次经期是几号
What was the date, duration
持续了多久  周期稳定吗
and consistency of your last period?
而你们老爸会使劲浑身解数
And your father would bend over backwards
博我一笑
trying to make me laugh.
一个牧师和一个犹太法师走进一家酒吧
A priest and a rabbi walk into a bar--
不  是家理发店  不  是邮局
no, a barbershop-- no, a post office--
不  是两个牧师  不  是两只鸭子
no, it's two priests-- no, it's two ducks--
不  是一个牧师抱着一只鸭子  是个波兰种
no, a priest holding a duck-- and he's Polish.
我是说牧师是波兰人  不是鸭子
The priest, not the duck.
其实鸭子也可以是波兰鸭
Actually, the duck could be Polish, too.
不过这没关系
Doesn't matter.
当然有关系  鸭子不是波兰鸭
Yes it does. The duck's not Polish.
如果还不能让我笑的话
And when that didn't work,
他真的会使尽"浑身"解数
he would actually bend over backwards.
屁股开花
Pratfall!
归根到底  我就是不想跟人倾诉
The bottom line is, I didn't feel like talking about it.
所以当泰德问起
So when Ted asked...
罗宾  你没事吧  你看起来很低落
Hey, Robin, you okay? You look upset.
我当时脱口而出撒了一个谎
I just came up with the first lie that popped into my head.
是啊
Yeah. Uh...
我发现我永远也无法
I just found out I can never...
成为加拿大国奥队的撑竿跳选手
be a pole-vaulter for the Canadian Olympic team.
可能我太高了吧
I'm too tall or something.
-罗宾  太遗憾了  -真是可惜  罗宾
- Robin, I'm sorry. - I'm so sorry, Robin.
-我居然不知情  -太糟糕了
- I had no idea. - That's terrible.
给我们上点烤鸡肉  快
Can we get some fried chicken over here, stat!
我真是不够朋友
I am such a bad friend!
三个放荡的修女出现在圣彼得
Three slutty nuns show up at St. Peter's--
慢着  她们不放荡
Wait, wait, they're not slutty.
她们的确很放荡  不过不应该一开始就告诉你
Well, they are, but you're not supposed to know that yet.
亲爱的  什么事
Hey, baby, what's up?
听着  搭建
Hey, uh, listen, the construction of
"光之交响乐"的进度
the Symphony of Illumination is taking
比我想象中慢
a little longer than I thought.
幸好我有斯科特帮忙
Good thing I have Scott here to help me.
对吧  斯科特
Right, Scott?
当然啦  埃先生
You betcha, Mr. E!
坏消息
Bad news.
罗宾因为身高过高  当不了国奥撑杆跳选手
Robin's too tall to be an Olympic pole-vaulter.
她向国际奥林匹克委员会提出申诉了吗
Has she filed an appeal with the IOC?
你向国际奥林匹克委员会提出申诉了吗
Have you filed an appeal with the IOC?
她能弯腰曲背让自己矮点吗
Can she make herself shorter by slouching?
你能弯腰曲背让自己矮点吗
Can you make yourself shorter by slouching?
她考虑过回学校
Has she considered going back to school
参加大学级别的比赛吗
and competing at the collegiate level?
你考虑过回学校参加...
Have you considered going back to school and...
我现在不想讨论这个
I don't want to talk about it.
对不起
Sorry.
我爱你  宝贝  明儿见
I love you, baby. See you tomorrow.
好的  我也爱你
Okay, I love you, too.
斯科特
Scott?
斯科特  我的手机掉下去了
Scott, I dropped my phone.
找到了
Yep, found it.
你能拿上来吗
Could you bring it up here?
没问题
You got it.
用我顺便帮你拿罐啤酒上去吗
Hey, while I'm at it, can I get you a beer?
他想给老头子拿罐啤酒
He wants to bring the old man a beer.
行  当然好啦
Yeah, sure.
冰箱里有一整箱
Uh, there's a whole case in the fridge.
谢谢你  孩子
Thanks, son.
你不介意我叫你"孩子"吧
Do you, do you mind if I call you "Son"?
你喜欢叫我什么都行
You can call me whatever you want...
混蛋
jackass.
斯科特Scott?
梯子倒了
The ladder fell.
斯科特
Scott?
马修年轻时常吃的大麻三明治
斯科特
Scott!
听我说
Listen, um,
我知道在这段时间里
I know things have been kind of weird
你和我的关系变得很奇怪
between you and me these past couple weeks,
我只想说
so I just want to say I'm...
我很开心我们又回到了原点
I'm glad we're back to where we started.
-对  -重新成为炮友
- Yeah. - Friends with benefits.
-不  -就像往常那样
- No. - Just like always.
从来不是炮友  只是朋友
Never been that. Just friends.
可以打炮的朋友  这事以后再议
With benefits. We'll talk about it later.
瞧瞧这屋子宝宝
Look at all these babies.
世界真奇妙  一旦知道你没有怀孕
Isn't it crazy how, now that we're not having one,
宝宝又变得可爱无比了
babies are cute again?
看那一个
Look at that one.
我不看了
I'm good.
不  我说真的  快看
No, I'm serious. Look, look.
我靠
Damn it.
这玩意儿太他妈可爱了
That thing's cute as crap.
天杀的  小可爱
Screw you, baby.
斯科特
Scott?
Scott!
这是怎么回事
What is going on?
-埃先生  -斯科特
- Hey, Mr. E. - Scott...
如果你不让我下来
if you do not let me down,
我就扯开嗓子叫到有人来帮忙
I am going to scream my head off until someone comes to help me,
到时候你可就要向警察解释这一切咯
and then you're going to have to explain all of this to the cops.
那你就必须解释
And then you'll have to explain why there's
为什么你的手机里有我的鸡鸡照
a picture of my ding-dong on your phone.
我手机里没有...
There is no picture of your...
现在有了
There is now.
哇  拍得太美了
Oh, yeah, that's a beauty.
斯科特
Scott?
Scott!
斯科特
马修一直
Marshall keeps
让我发咪咪的照片给他
asking me to text him pictures of my boobies.
都老夫老妻这么多年了
After all these years,
他还会时不时像个孩子一样闹我
he sometimes still acts like a teenager.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
疯子杜安
Insane Duane.
现在是常人杜安了
It's Sane Duane now.
你以前可是个伟人呀
You used to be magnificent.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事  没事  我想
Yeah, yeah, um, I guess this, um,
撑杆跳这件事真的打击到我了
this pole-vaulting thing is finally hitting me.
我不明白  罗宾
I don't get it, Robin.
你真想成为一个撑杆跳选手吗
Did you really want to be a pole-vaulter?
不不  我其实
No, no, I was, uh,
一直坚决抵制...
I was always adamantly against having a...
成为撑杆跳选手
uh, a pole-vaulting career,
即使这是很多女人梦寐以求的事
even though it's what most women want.
撑杆跳是很多女人梦寐以求的吗
Most women want to be a pole-vaulter?
在加拿大是  人们非常喜欢这项运动
In Canada-- it's very big up there.
生活就是  遇见对的人
You know, it's, it's meet a nice guy,
结婚  偶尔撑两杆
get married, vault some poles,
但我...
but I...
从来不想要那种生活
never wanted that.
当然  不想要是一回事
Of course, it's one thing not to want something.
不能要又是另外一回事了
It's another to be told you can't have it.
我真心觉得  只要回心转意
I guess it's, it's just nice knowing
还有能力做这件事  该多好呀
that you could someday do it if you changed your mind.
而现在  通往那种生活的大门  突然间就关上了
But now, all of a sudden, that door is closed.
那个一边滑雪一边射击的运动呢
What about the one where you ski and shoot at the same time?
你挺擅长那个的
That seems like something you'd be good at.
天啊  罗宾  看这个
Oh, my God, Robin, look at this.
加拿大小可爱
O Cana-dorable!
对不对
Am I right?
失陪一下
Excuse me.
这玩意真的有效
Yep, this works.
斯科特  等我下来
Scott, when I get down from here,
你麻烦就大了  老兄
you are going to be in big, big trouble, mister.
别这样  埃先生
Come on, Mr. E.
你小时候就没放纵过吗
Didn't you ever cut loose when you were a kid?
不要转移话题
That's irrelevant.
我当然放纵过
I mean, of course I did.
有一次  我父母出城去了
One time, when my parents were out of town,
我和几个哥哥办了一场业余摔跤表演
my brothers and I set the basement on fire
结果把地下室烧着了
hosting an amateur wrestling exhibition.
因为我们还搞了些舞台效果
There were some theatrics.
看  你能理解我吧
See, you get me.
你和其他被我困在屋顶的傻瓜不一样
I don't think of you as some dummy I trapped on the roof.
我更愿意把你看成  我的爸爸
I think of you more like, like my dad.
能让我们的派对再开半小时吗  求你了
Can we keep the party going for 30 more minutes, please?
好吧  斯科特
Okay, Scott.
谢了  老爹
Thanks, Pop.
没事  孩子也是需要发泄一下精力的
It's fine, kid just needed to blow off some steam.
不
No!
那是冈德森祖母亲手织的
Grandma Gunderson knitted that!
斯科特
Scott...!
太可怕了
That was crazy.
她就这样哭着跑了出去
She just ran out of there crying.
她也不接电话
Now she's not answering her phone.
自从我们那晚回忆了飓风之夜后
She's been acting really weird for a few weeks now,
她最近几周表现都很反常
really since the night we discussed the hurricane.
巴尼  你和她拼车回家
Barney, you split a cab home.
她有跟你说什么吗
Did she say anything?
我俩其实没怎么说话
We didn't really talk much.
幸好
Well, lucky for us,
这里的某人颇为擅长
someone at this table is skilled
侦查推理之术
in the art of detection.
罗宾很难过
Robin's upset.
她和凯文之间出了问题
She and Kevin are having trouble.
-他出轨了  -不可能
- He cheated on her. - No way.
凯文是个诚实正派的人
Kevin's an honest, decent guy
况且就算他状态最好的那天
who never on his best day
也泡不到比罗宾好的妞了
could pull a hotter chick than Robin.
那也许是罗宾出轨了
Maybe Robin cheated on him.
也许是罗宾这枝红杏  伸出了墙外
Maybe Robin is the dirty bird who slept with someone else.
我觉得撑杆跳这件事
I don't know, this pole-vaulting thing seems
才是那个让她崩溃的点
like a slam dunk to me.
太明显了
Oh, it is so obvious.
巴尼
Barney.
你那个同事
What is the name of that guy
叫什么来着  兰迪
you worked with-- uh, Randy?
就是那个兰迪
It was Randy.
等等
Wait a second.
我刚刚破解了事情的真相
I just cracked this case.
那件枫叶婴儿装
The little maple leaf onesie.
让罗宾想家了
It made her homesick.
所以她才如此难过
That's why she's so upset.
她不回家过圣诞节
She's not going home for Christmas.
她想让我邀请她去俄亥俄过节
She wants me to invite her to Ohio.
肯定就是这样了
That's got to be it!
要不然就是她和巴尼睡了
Either that or she slept with Barney.
你一定是斯科特吧
Oh, you must be Scott.
太太  你好
Oh, hello, ma'am.
总算见到"庐峰"真面目了
It's nice to finally see your face.
我得回家温书去了
Well, I'd better go hit those books.
少年  请留步
Hold it right there, young man.
这是你帮助我先生的奖励
This is for helping out my husband.
五十大洋
Wow, 50 bucks.
祝你圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
莉莉
Lily!
一张去克利夫兰的机票
An airplane ticket to Cleveland?
虽然不是你家  但好歹都是家
I know it's not Canada, but it starts with a "C"
而且也冷得蛋疼  所以快去准备行李吧
and it's cold as balls, so get packed.
你跟我一起回家过圣诞节
You're coming home with me for Christmas.
想法不错  老兄
Yeah, nice try, dude.
就算六年能挣一亿二千五百万
I wouldn't go to Cleveland for $125 million
我也不去克利夫兰
paid over six years.
勒布朗・詹姆斯曾为克利夫兰骑士队效力了六年
薪水总额为一亿二千五百万
又是这个
Still?
勒布朗的玩笑你要开到什么时候
Still with the LeBron jokes?
勒布朗后来为总冠军加盟迈阿密热火
于10-11总决赛败给小牛队与冠军失之交臂
冠军戒指在哪里
Where's that ring, huh?
他本该得到的总冠军戒指在哪里
Where's that ring he's supposed to have by now?
我还以为你是因为不能回家
Look, I just-- I thought you were bummed
过圣诞节而沮丧呢
about not going home for Christmas.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我喜欢圣诞时节的纽约
I love New York at Christmas.
宁静而平和
It's so quiet and peaceful.
还有蛋酒与我为伴
Got my eggnog to keep me company, so...
罗宾  到底怎么回事
Robin, what's wrong?
-没事啊  -告诉我吧
- Nothing. - Just tell me.
你干嘛这么想知道
Why do you need to know so bad?
然后我才能帮你打气呀
So I can cheer you up.
为我打气又不是你的职责
It's not your job to cheer me up.
是的  没错
Yes, it is.
为你打气就是我职责所在
Cheering you up is my job.
好  你被开除了
Well, then, you're fired.
你不能开除我
You can't fire me.
我可有工会撑腰  贱人
I'm union, bitch.
为我打气不是你的责任
It's not your job to cheer me up.
-就是  -不是
- Yes, it is. - No, it's not.
就是
Yes, it is.
我说不是就不是
No, it's not.
圣诞快乐  泰德
Merry Christmas, Ted.
你也圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
孩子们  我独自一人过圣诞节
So, kids, I settled in for a Christmas alone.
我很感激泰德想为我打气
I appreciated that Ted wanted to cheer me up,
可说真的  没必要
but honestly, it wasn't necessary.
就算我不能生孩子
So I can't have kids.
那又怎样
Big deal.
这样我的人生少了羁绊
This way there's no one to hold me back in life,
没人能阻止我去云游四海
no one to keep me from traveling where I want to travel,
没人能阻止我去打拼事业
no one getting in the way of my career.
如果你们想知道真相
If you want to know the truth of it,
我很庆幸  你们从未存在
I'm glad you guys aren't real.
真心庆幸
Really glad.
妈的
Damn it.
为你打气乃我职责所在
Yes, it is.
你不想告诉我出了什么事  没关系
Look, you don't want to tell me what's wrong, fine.
我不需要知道
I don't need to know.
可你永远阻止不了我为你加油打气
But you can never stop me from trying to cheer you up.
这是无法改变的事实
It's a fact of life.
你还是学着适应吧
You're just gonna have to deal with it.
泰德
Ted...
AC/DC《Highway To Hell》
等一下  这部分是最棒的
Hold on, hold on, this is the best part.
我在直通地狱的路上飞驰 *
* I'm on the highway to hell
直通地狱 *
* On the highway to hell
* Highway to hell...
孩子们  罗宾阿姨从未成为撑杆跳健将
Kids, your Aunt Robin never became a pole-vaulter,
但她成为了著名的记者
but she did become a famous journalist,
成功的女商人  环球旅行家
a successful businesswoman, a world traveler.
她还短暂地当过斗牛士
She was even briefly a bullfighter--
那是个有趣的故事  以后再告诉你们
that's a funny story, I'll get to that one later.
你们罗宾阿姨一生只从未做过一件事
But there's one thing your Aunt Robin never was.
她从未独自一人
She was never alone.